（嗖嗖）
(swoosh)
- [旁白] 嗨，这将是一个视频
- [Narrator] Hi, this is going to be a video
关于 push_to_hub API
about the push_to_hub API
适用于 Tensorflow 和 Keras。
for Tensorflow and Keras.
因此，首先，我们将打开我们的笔记本。
So, to get started, we'll open up our notebook.
你需要做的第一件事就是登录
And the first thing you'll need to do is log in to
你的 HuggingFace 帐户，
your HuggingFace account,
例如笔记本登录功能。
for example with the notebook login function.
所以要使用它，你只需调用函数，
So to use that, you simply call the function,
弹出窗口将出现。
the popup will emerge.
你将输入你的用户名和密码，
You will enter your username and password,
我要在这里从我的密码管理器中取出，
which I'm going to pull out of my password manager here,
然后你登录。
and you log in.
接下来的两个单元格只是
The next two cells are just
为训练做好一切准备。
getting everything ready for training.
所以我们只是要加载一个数据集，
So we're just going to load a dataset,
我们要标记那个数据集，
we're going to tokenize that dataset,
然后我们将加载我们的模型并编译
and then we're going to load our model and compile
它与标准的 Adam 优化器。
it with the standard Adam optimizer.
所以我将运行所有这些。
So I'm just going to run all of those.
我们等几秒钟，
We'll wait a few seconds,
一切都应该为训练做好准备。
and everything should be ready for training.
好的。
Okay.
所以现在我们准备好训练了。
So now we're ready to train.
我将向你展示两种方法
I'm going to show you the two ways
你可以将你的模型推送到 Hub。
you can push your model to the Hub.
所以第一个是 PushToHubCallback。
So the first is with the PushToHubCallback.
所以在 Keras 中回调
So a callback in Keras
是在训练期间定期调用的函数。
is a function that's called regularly during training.
你可以将其设置为在一定数量的步骤后调用，
You can set it to be called after a certain number of steps,
或每个时期，甚至只是在训练结束时一次。
or every epoch, or even just once at the end of training.
所以 Keras 中有很多回调，例如，
So a lot of callbacks in Keras, for example,
控制学习率在高原上衰减，
control learning rate decaying on plateau,
诸如此类的事情。
and things like that.
所以这个回调，默认情况下，
So this callback, by default,
每个时期都会将你的模型保存到 Hub 一次。
will save your model to the Hub once every epoch.
这真的很有帮助，
And that's really helpful,
特别是如果你的训练时间很长，
especially if your training is very long,
因为那意味着你可以从那个保存中恢复，
because that means you can resume from that save,
所以你得到了你的模型的自动云保存。
so you get this automatic cloud-saving of your model.
你甚至可以进行推理
And you can even run inference
使用模型的检查点
with the checkpoints of your model
已通过此回调上传。
that have been uploaded by this callback.
这意味着你可以，
And that means you can,
你知道，运行一些测试输入
y'know, run some test inputs
并实际查看你的模型是如何工作的
and actually see how your model works
在训练的各个阶段，
at various stages during training,
这是一个非常好的功能。
which is a really nice feature.
所以我们要添加 PushToHubCallback，
So we're going to add the PushToHubCallback,
它只需要几个参数。
and it takes just a few arguments.
所以第一个参数是临时目录
So the first argument is the temporary directory
该文件将被保存到
that files are going to be saved to
在将它们上传到 Hub 之前。
before they're uploaded to the Hub.
第二个参数是分词器，
The second argument is the tokenizer,
第三个参数在这里
and the third argument here
是关键字参数 hub_model_id。
is the keyword argument hub_model_id.
所以这就是它将被保存的名称
So that's the name it's going to be saved under
在 HuggingFace Hub 上。
on the HuggingFace Hub.
你还可以上传到组织帐户
You can also upload to an organization account
只需添加组织名称
just by adding the organization name
在带有斜杠的存储库名称之前，就像这样。
before the repository name with a slash, like this.
所以你可能没有权限
So you probably don't have permissions
上传到 HuggingFace 组织，
to upload to the HuggingFace organization,
如果你这样做请提交错误
if you do please file a bug
并非常紧急地通知我们。
and let us know extremely urgently.
但如果你确实有权访问你自己的组织，
But if you do have access to your own organization,
那么你可以使用相同的方法
then you can use that same approach
将模型上传到他们的帐户
to upload models to their account
而不是你自己的个人模型集。
instead of to your own personal set of models.
所以，一旦你回电了，
So, once you've made your callback,
你只需将它添加到回调列表
you simply add it to the callbacks list
当你调用 model.fit 时。
when you're calling model.fit.
一切都从那里为你上传，
And everything is uploaded for you from there,
没有什么可担心的。
there's nothing else to worry about.
上传模型的第二种方式，
The second way to upload a model, though,
就是调用 model.push_to_hub。
is to call model.push_to_hub.
所以这更像是一种一次性的方法。
So this is more of a once-off method.
在训练期间不会定期调用它。
It's not called regularly during training.
你可以随时手动调用它
You can just call this manually whenever you want to
将模型上传到集线器。
upload a model to the hub.
所以我们建议在训练结束后运行这个，
So we recommend running this after the end of training,
只是为了确保你有一条提交消息
just to make sure that you have a commit message
保证这是最终版本
to guarantee that this was the final version
训练结束时的模型。
of the model at the end of training.
它只是确保，你知道，
And it just makes sure that, you know,
你正在使用最终的训练结束模型
you're working with the definitive end-of-training model
而不是不小心使用检查点
and not accidentally using a checkpoint
从沿途的某个地方。
from somewhere along the way.
所以我要运行这两个单元格。
So I'm going to run both of these cells.
然后我要在这里剪视频，
And then I'm going to cut the video here,
只是因为训练需要几分钟。
just because training is going to take a couple of minutes.
所以我会跳到最后，
So I'll skip forward to the end of that,
当模型全部上传后，
when the models have all been uploaded,
我会告诉你怎么做
and I'm gonna show you how you can
访问 Hub 中的模型，
access the models in the Hub,
以及你可以从那里用它们做的其他事情。
and the other things you can do with them from there.
好的，我们回来了，
Okay, we're back,
我们的模型已上传。
and our model was uploaded.
两者都由 PushToHubCallback
Both by the PushToHubCallback
以及我们在训练后调用 model.push_to_hub。
and also by our call to model.push_to_hub after training.
所以一切看起来都很好。
So everything's looking good.
所以现在如果我们转到我在 HuggingFace 上的个人资料，
So now if we drop over to my profile on HuggingFace,
你只需点击个人资料按钮就可以到达那里
and you can get there just by clicking the profile button
在下拉列表中。
in the dropdown.
我们可以看到 bert-fine-tuned-cola 模型在这里，
We can see that the bert-fine-tuned-cola model is here,
并于 3 分钟前更新。
and was updated 3 minutes ago.
所以它总是在你的列表的顶部，
So it'll always be at the top of your list,
因为它们是按最近更新时间排序的。
because they're sorted by how recently they were updated.
我们可以立即开始查询我们的模型。
And we can start querying our model immediately.
所以我们训练的数据集
So the dataset we were training on
是 Glue CoLA 数据集，
is the Glue CoLA dataset,
CoLA 是代表
and CoLA is an acronym standing for
语言可接受性语料库。
the Corpus of Linguistic Acceptability.
所以这意味着正在训练模型来决定
So what that means is the model is being trained to decide
如果一个句子在语法或语言上没问题，
if a sentence is grammatically or linguistically okay,
或者它是否有问题。
or if there's a problem with it.
例如，我们可以说，“这是一个合法的句子。”
For example, we could say, "This is a legitimate sentence."
希望它意识到
And hopefully it realizes that
这实际上是一个合法的判决。
this is in fact a legitimate sentence.
所以加载模型可能需要几秒钟
So it might take a couple of seconds for the model to load
当你第一次调用它时。
when you call it for the first time.
所以我可能会在这里从这个视频中剪掉几秒钟。
So I might cut a couple of seconds out of this video here.
好的，我们回来了。
Okay, we're back.
所以模型加载了，我们得到了一个输出，
So the model loaded and we got an output,
但这里有一个明显的问题。
but there's an obvious problem here.
所以这些标签并没有真正告诉我们
So these labels aren't really telling us
模型实际分配了哪些类别
what categories the model has actually assigned
到这个输入句子。
to this input sentence.
所以如果我们想解决这个问题，
So if we want to fix that,
我们要确保模型配置
we want to make sure the model config
每个标签类别都有正确的名称，
has the correct names for each of the label classes,
然后我们要上传该配置。
and then we want to upload that config.
所以我们可以在这里做。
So we can do that down here.
要获取标签名称，
To get the label names,
我们可以从我们加载的数据集中得到它，
we can get that from the dataset we loaded,
从它具有的特性属性。
from the features attribute it has.
然后我们可以创建字典
And then we can create dictionaries
“id2label” 和 “label2id”，
"id2label" and "label2id",
并将它们分配给模型配置。
and just assign them to the model config.
然后我们可以推送我们更新的配置，
And then we can just push our updated config,
这将覆盖 Hub 存储库中的现有配置。
and that'll override the existing config in the Hub repo.
所以这已经完成了。
So that's just been done.
所以现在，如果我们回到这里，
So now, if we go back here,
我要用一个稍微不同的句子
I'm going to use a slightly different sentence
因为句子的输出有时会被缓存。
because the outputs for sentences are sometimes cached.
所以，如果我们想产生新的结果
And so, if we want to generate new results
我将使用一些稍微不同的东西。
I'm going to use something slightly different.
因此，让我们尝试一个不正确的句子。
So let's try an incorrect sentence.
所以这不是有效的英语语法
So this is not valid English grammar
希望模型能看到这一点。
and hopefully the model will see that.
它会在这里重新加载，
It's going to reload here,
所以我要在这里缩短几秒钟，
so I'm going to cut a couple of seconds here,
然后我们会看到模型会说什么。
and then we'll see what the model is going to say.
好的。
Okay.
所以这个模型，它的信心不是很好，
So the model, it's confidence isn't very good,
因为我们当然没有真正优化
because of course we didn't really optimize
我们的超参数。
our hyperparameters at all.
但它决定了这句话
But it has decided that this sentence
不可接受的可能性大于可接受的可能性。
is more likely to be unacceptable than acceptable.
大概如果我们更努力地训练
Presumably if we tried a bit harder with training
我们可以获得更低的验证损失，
we could get a much lower validation loss,
因此模型的预测会更准确。
and therefore the model's predictions would be more precise.
但是让我们再试一次我们原来的句子。
But let's try our original sentence again.
当然，因为缓存的问题，
Of course, because of the caching issue,
我们看到原来的答案没有改变。
we're seeing that the original answers are unchanged.
所以让我们尝试一个不同的，有效的句子。
So let's try a different, valid sentence.
所以让我们试试，“This is a valid English sentence”。
So let's try, "This is a valid English sentence".
我们看到现在模型正确地决定了
And we see that now the model correctly decides
它被接受的可能性非常高，
that it has a very high probability of being acceptable,
并且被拒绝的可能性非常低。
and a very low probability of being unacceptable.
所以你可以使用这个推理 API
So you can use this inference API
即使有训练期间上传的检查点，
even with the checkpoints that are uploaded during training,
所以看看如何
so it can be very interesting to see how
模型对样本输入的预测发生变化
the model's predictions for sample inputs change
在每个训练阶段。
with each epoch of training.
另外，我们上传的模型
Also, the model we've uploaded
你将可以访问，并且
is going to be accessible to you and,
如果公开分享给其他任何人。
if it's shared publicly, to anyone else.
所以如果你想加载那个模型，
So if you want to load that model,
你或其他任何人需要做的一切
all you or anyone else needs to do
只是将它加载到管道中，
is just to load it in either a pipeline,
或者你可以加载它，例如，
or you can just load it with, for example,
TFAutoModelForSequenceClassification。
TFAutoModelForSequenceClassification.
然后对于名称，你只需通过
And then for the name you would just simply pass
你要上传的存储库的路径。
the path to the repo you want to upload.
或者下载，不好意思。
Or to download, excuse me.
所以如果我想再次使用这个模型，
So if I want to use this model again,
如果我想从集线器加载它，
if I want to load it from the hub,
我只是运行这一行代码。
I just run this one line of code.
该模型将被下载。
The model will be downloaded.
而且，运气好的话，它会准备好
And, with any luck, it'll be ready to
对不同的数据集进行微调，进行预测，
fine-tune on a different dataset, make predictions with,
或者做任何你想做的事情。
or do anything else you wanna do.
所以这是对如何的快速概述，
So that was a quick overview of how,
在你训练之后或训练期间，
after your training or during your training,
你可以将模型上传到 Hub，
you can upload models to the Hub,
你可以在那里检查站，
you can checkpoint there,
你可以从那里恢复训练，
you can resume training from there,
你可以得到推理结果
and you can get inference results
来自你上传的模型。
from the models you've uploaded.
所以谢谢你，我希望在以后的视频中见到你。
So thank you, and I hope to see you in a future video.
（嗖嗖）
(swoosh)